
State your name   
An alien from some distant planet got lost in our world. He asks you to find his compatriots and contact them. To search the Internet for them, fill the value of the regex variable with a regular expression that matches common names of the inhabitants of that planet. The names are developed according to the following rules:  the first symbol is an alphanumeric character the second symbol is a digit there may be another digit following the first one the last symbol is not a whitespace or alphanumeric character  
Strange rules, indeed, but who are we to judge them?  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
