
List from string   
Write a program that constructs a list from the given string's symbols and then prints it. 
So, if input_str, for example, contains a string "python", your program should turn it to the list ['p', 'y', 't', 'h', 'o', 'n'] and print it.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
