
Searching for a book   
You are looking for a rare book in multiple online stores. To automate the process, you want to write Python code that would collect the search results for you. 
Define a function do_search(bookstore_url, params) that takes the url of the store bookstore_url and the dictionary of the search parameters params, sends a GET request to the page with the search results and returns the response object. 
For instance, if bookstore_url = 'http://bookstore.com/search' and params = {'author': 'Austen', 'title': 'Emma'}, the response object should contain the data retrieved from http://bookstore.com/search?author=Austennamp;title=Emma. 
Note that you do not need to read any input or call the function do_search() yourself.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 30 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
