Time Open on Hyperskill

  
Here's a class named Time with three fields: hours, minutes and seconds. 
nnbsp; 
Add three constructors to the class: 
nnbsp;  The first one takes only hours and initializes this field; The second one takes hours and minutes and initializes the corresponding fields; The third one takes hours, minutes and seconds and initializes all fields.  
Do not make the fields and constructors private.  Memory limit: 256 MbTime limit: 5s
Show topic summary
