
Batman   
Here's a class representing Batman, the protector of Gotham. This class uses the standard constructor (no parameters) and has a method intimidate_villain that doesn't take any parameters. This class is already created, you do NOT need to create it. 
Your task, on the other hand, is to create an instance of the class Batman and call the method intimidate_villain. Do NOT print anything.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
