Bank account Open on Hyperskill

  
You are given a class named BankAccount. The class has two fields: number and balance. 
Define two classes which inherit from the BankAccount:  CheckingAccount containing the double field fee. SavingAccount containing the double field interestRate.  
Each new class should have a constructor with three parameters to initialize all fields:  CheckingAccount(Stringnnbsp;number,nnbsp;Longnnbsp;balance,nnbsp;doublennbsp;fee) SavingAccount(Stringnnbsp;number,nnbsp;Longnnbsp;balance,nnbsp;doublennbsp;interestRate)  
Do not forget to invoke the superclass constructor when creating objects. 
Do not make the fields private.  Memory limit: 256 MbTime limit: 5s
Show topic summary
