
Find the password   
 
Imagine that you are a hacker and you have got access to a web server written in Python. The problem is that it asks for a password that you do not know. However, this server is open source so you know that there is the wrong_password() function which takes a password and checks it against real_password. 
def wrong_password(password): return (password == "" or (not password and real_password)) or password != real_password You can not access the real_password variable but you can call the wrong_password() function and exploit its vulnerability to obtain the password. Write your code inside the solve() function. Think about an argument that can be passed to the wrong_password() function so that the function returns the real_password. Print the result of the wrong_password() function. 
Your program should not read any input or call the solve() function, your task is to implement it. 
 Hint   
 Remember that "and" and "or" operators return one of their operands. Refer to the tables showing which operands the operators return in different cases.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
