
Octahedron   
Write a program that reads a positive integer representing edge length of the regular octahedron and prints two values â€“ its area and volume, both rounded to 2 decimal places and split by one space. A regular octahedron is a polyhedron with eight equal faces and twelve equal edges. To calculate the area of an octahedron, use the following formula: \(2 \sqrt{3} a ^ 2\) , where a is edge length. To calculate the volume, use the following formula: \(\frac{1}{3} \sqrt{2} a ^ 3\).  Sample Input:63Sample Output:13749.02 117873.29Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
