
Adelie locator   
Imagine you have a full Penguins dataset: 
penguins_df.head()  
Select all Adelie penguins and take every second column from the island column (i.e. island, bill_depth_mm, body_mass_g), then print the resulting data frame.   Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
