
Unnecessary digits   
You have a problem with your dataset: you collected a list of names but it has been accidentally mixed up with various digits that you do not need. Given a string of corrupted names, remove all digits using regexps and print a list of names.  
 Hint   
 We are sure that you should use re.split() in this case.  
  Sample Input:John2Mary365Jane56MichaelSample Output:['John', 'Mary', 'Jane', 'Michael']Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
