
Full name   
In the code below, you can see a program that creates a full name from the first and last names for several people.  
name1 = "John" last_name1 = "Lennon" full_name1 = name1 + " " + last_name1 name2 = "Hermione" last_name2 = "Granger" full_name2 = name2 + " " + last_name2 Wouldn't it be much easier if we had a function that could do the same? 
Your task is to write the body of the function create_full_name that takes name and last_name (in this order) and returns the full name.  
Do NOT change the variable names. You don't need to call the function yourself.   Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
