
Difference of times   
You will get the values for two moments in time of the same day: when Megan went for a walk, and when it started to rain. It is known that the first event happened earlier than the second one. Find out how many seconds passed between them. 
The program gets the input of six integers, each on a separate line. The first three integers represent hours, minutes, and seconds of the first event, and the rest three integers define similarly the second event. Print the number of seconds between these two moments of time.  Sample Input:111222Sample Output:3661Sample Input:12301320Sample Output:50Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 1 second Show topic summary
