Blacklist Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Has it ever bothered you whennnbsp;unknown people call you and try to impose their services? That can be annoying. 
Let's try to solve the problem by using blacklist. You should implement the filterPhones method that returns only thennbsp;phone numbers that are not on the blacklist. 
 Hint   
 The simplest way to do it is to use the contains method, for-each loop and one more collection.  
 nnbsp;  Sample Input:387-968-2999 505-468-5235 739-738-3272505-468-5235Sample Output:387-968-2999 739-738-3272Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
