
Film   
Write a program that gets information about a movie from the input and presents in the following format: 
movie (dir. director) came out in year 
The input format: 
3 lines: first the title of the movie, then the name of the director and then the year of its release.  Sample Input:Fight ClubDavid Fincher1999Sample Output:Fight Club (dir. David Fincher) came out in 1999Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
