Message notifier as a thread Open on JetBrains Academy    
Write a service that takes a message and the number of its repetitions as constructor parameters and prints the message in the standard output the specified number of times. 
Use the provided template for your class. 
The testing system will start the service as a regular thread.  Sample Input:Hello, Mary3Sample Output:Hello, MaryHello, MaryHello, MaryMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
