
Even numbers   
Create a function called even() that takes a number as an argument. If the number is even, return it. Otherwise, use the assert keyword. 
You do not need to take any input or call the function yourself.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
