Max and Min Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Use the strategy pattern to implement algorithms to find max and min values in a given array. The basic structure of the provided classes is described below: your job is to complete it. 
The class Finder represents the general finding algorithm itself. It has find(int[] numbers) method that returns the result of finding according to the specified strategy. 
The interface FindingStrategy provides getResult() methodnnbsp;to write new concrete finding strategies. 
Please, do not change the interface FindingStrategy, and do not rename the existing methods. 
If the array is empty, the Finder should return Integer.MAX_VALUE in case of finding the min value and Integer.MIN_VALUE in case of finding the max value. 
HINT: tests 1-5 check MinFindingStrategy, tests 6-10 check MaxFindingStrategy. Do not forget to check your solution when the passed array has the size 0 or 1.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
