
Calculating S V P   
Ask the user about parameters of a rectangular parallelepiped (3 integers representing the length, width and height) and print the sum of edge lengths, its total surface area and volume. 
Sum of lengths of all edges: 
\(s = 4(a + b + c)\) 
Surface area: 
\(S = 2(ab + bc + ac)\) 
Volume: 
\(V = abc\)  Sample Input:51015Sample Output:120550750Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
