
British to American   
It is known that British English and American English speakers spell some words differently â€” colour and color, flavour and flavor, humour and humor. 
Your task is to write a program that converts the input text so that British words containing the -ou- syllable are swapped with their Americanized version (-o-).   Sample Input:I love this colour!Sample Output:I love this color!Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
