
Equation   
Write a function equation_writing() that will print the equation in the following format: a x + b = c. The function must take three arguments: a, b, c, these values are subject to change. The rest of the equation remains unchanged. 
You are NOT supposed to handle input or call a function, just implement it.  Sample Input:3 4 3Sample Output:3 x + 4 = 3Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
