
Fix str   
The previous developer accidentally named a variable str. Since this name is reserved for a built-in type, now the code fails. 
Please fix the variable name by adding an underscore, as suggested in the topic. The value of your new variable shouldn't change, i.e. it should look like Hello10. You don't have to print anything.  
Remember that the str() function returns the string version of the given object. 
 Hint   
 You should NOT create a new variable in the second line. Use the same variable as you used in the first line.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
