Ternary predicate Open on JetBrains Academy    
You need to write your own functional interface (TernaryIntPredicate) and use it with a lambda expression. The interface must have a single non-static (and non-default) method test with three int arguments that returns boolean value.Besides, you need to write a lambda expression with three int arguments using your TernaryIntPredicate.  The lambda expression has to return true if all passed values are different  otherwise  false. The name of the instance is allValuesAreDifferentPredicate. It should be a static field. Important. Use the provided template for your solution. Do not change it!    Sample Input:1 1 1Sample Output:FalseSample Input:2 3 4Sample Output:TrueMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
