
Tokenizing a particular sentence in the text   
There is a text and also an integer in the input. You need to split the text into sentences. Use a number (the second line in the input) as an index for choosing a sentence from the list. Tokenize this sentence using the pattern "[A-z']+" and print it. 
 Hint   
 Do not forget to import the modules you need  
  Sample Input:Meet the Greens! They've got a big house on the outskirts of Leeds. There are 15 rooms in it.2Sample Output:['There', 'are', 'rooms', 'in', 'it']Memory limit: 512 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
