Find the nearest number Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Write a program that finds out the closest integer to a given one from an array.nnbsp;If you find several integers with the same distance to the N, you should output all of them in the ascending order. If the are several equal numbers, output them all. 
Input: a set of integersnnbsp;and a number N.nnbsp;nnbsp; 
Output: some number(s) from the given array.  Sample Input:1 2 4 53Sample Output:2 4Sample Input:1 2 3 46Sample Output:4Sample Input:5 1 3 3 1 54Sample Output:3 3 5 5Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
