
Write the template   
Fill the template variable value in the code in such a way that would make it match the first three of the following strings and not match the fourth one: string_1 = 'I love Python 3' string_2 = 'i love Pitsaw' string_3 = 'we love Papuan' string_4 = 'we love php'  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
