
Asking for help   
Let's say you need the isdir() function from the os.path module, but you don't know how it works. Recall which built-in function we can use to access documentation and find the docstring of os.path.isdir() . You do not need to use print(). 
 Hint   
 You should pass os.path.isdir() without parentheses to the function. That's so because we don't need to execute it here â€” we simply refer to isdir() as an object.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
