Iterations Open on JetBrains Academy    
There are two static methods: 
1) static void performIterationsWithCallback(int numberOfIterations, LoopCallback callback) 2) static void startIterations(int numberOfIterations) The first method takes a number of iterations for a loop and a callback that is called on each iteration. The second method takes a number of iterations, creates a callback and passes them to the first method. 
The LoopCallback interface has a single method: 
interface LoopCallback { void onNewIteration(int iteration); } You should implement the second method. It must create an instance of an anonymous class that implements LoopCallback and passes it to the first method. The overridden method onNewIteration should output the number of iteration to the standard output on a separate line. For example: 
Iteration: 0 Use the provided code template.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
