
We Are What We Eat   Anthony keeps track of what he eats: he writes down how many calories are in his meals. Use the list of dictionaries to calculate the total amount of calories per day and print it. 
 
The sample input will look like: 
meals = [ {"title": "Oatmeal pancakes with apple and cinnamon", "kcal": 370}, {"title": "Italian salad with fusilli and ham", "kcal": 320}, {"title": "Bulgur with vegetables", "kcal": 350}, {"title": "Curd souffle with lingonberries and ginger", "kcal": 225}, {"title": "Oatmeal with honey and peanuts", "kcal": 440}] The output in this case should be 1705. 
 Hint   
 We hope you will use the pair "kcal" : value.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
