
Success or fail?   
Define a function check_success(url) that, given a URL, sends out a GET request and returns "Success" if it succeeds and "Fail" otherwise. 
 Hint   
 Remember that the status codes between 200 and 399 indicate that the request succeeded, while all the codes starting with a 4 signalize an error.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 30 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
