
Hello, Python   
Here is a simple one-line Python program that prints a text. Copy it to the text area below and then click the Run button (or Check button if you use an IDE). Our server will verify whether the program is correct and will tell you the result. 
print("Learn Python to be great!") Now, you do not need to understand how the program works, just enjoy it! :)  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
