Pow Open on JetBrains Academy    
You are given two floating-point numbers: a and b. 
Calculate and output the value of the expression a^b. 
Note: use double variables for a and b. 
Input data format: 
Two floating-point numbers in one line. 
Output data format: 
The result of the expression.  
Sample Input:2 3
Sample Output:8.0
Sample Input:2 1.02
Sample Output:
2.027918959580058
Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
