String processor Open on JetBrains Academy    
 Write a class with the name  StringProcessor  that extends the  Thread  class  . The class must have a method that reads strings (line by line) from the standard input. If a read string has a character in lower case, the processor must output the string in the upper case; otherwise, the processor must output "FINISHED" and stop the processing.   
   
 Use the provided template for your class. Write any additional methods if you need them.   
 The testing system will start the processor as a regular thread.   Sample Input:lineLINESample Output:LINEFINISHEDSample Input:threadSPROCeSSESTASKSSample Output:THREADSPROCESSESFINISHEDMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
