
Implement a function   
Write the code that corresponds to the docstring of the function. In the code, you should check whether the input number is positive, otherwise, it should return the string "Enter a positive number!". Note that zero is neither a positive nor a negative number. 
You don't need to take any input or call the function. Just write the body of get_number().  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
