IntBinaryOperation Open on JetBrains Academy

  
You are given an abstract class IntBinaryOperation. It has one abstract method perform() and two fields representing the operation arguments. The fields are initialized in the constructor. See the provided code template. 
You need to declare and implement two classes representing concrete operations: Addition and Multiplication. The classes must extend the abstract class and implement the method perform(). The implementations should work in accordance with the class name. Do not forget to write two-argument constructors in your classes. 
Do NOT make your classes public.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
