
Finding pets   
Your next task is to compile a pattern called pets that matches the following pets: dog, cat, parrot, and hamster. Your pattern must be case-insensitive, so uppercase and lowercase characters must be treated equally.  
You will receive a string as an input. You need to print out a list of found pets.  Sample Input:I love Dogs and cats!Sample Output:['Dog', 'cat']Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
