
Tourists   
Eugene and Rose decided to travel abroad. For convenience, they will go to a country where one of them has already been, but not where they both have. 
Output a set of potential countries for them. 
 Hint   
 If you feel up to trying something new, use set.symmetric_difference(other), which returns a new set that contains all items from both sets, except for their common elements.  
  Sample Input:Greece Netherlands Colombia UKItaly UK Russia Greece CanadaSample Output:{'Colombia', 'Russia', 'Italy', 'Netherlands', 'Canada'}Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
