Return empty string when argument is null Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Take a look at thennbsp;method that takes a string, converts all characters of the string to the upper case and then returns the resulting string. 
But there is a problem. Sometimes an input string is null. As you already know, innnbsp;this case,nnbsp;the method throws NullPointerException. 
Your task is to fix the method in order to avoid NPE. 
If the input string is null, the method should return the empty string "".  Sample Input:a stringSample Output:A STRINGMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
