Mutable geometric shapes Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Suppose, you are writing a geometric engine. Now it includes classesnnbsp;Circle, Rectanglennbsp;and interfacesnnbsp;Movable and Scalable. 
 
nnbsp; 
You need:  to write a new interface MutableShape that extends both existing interfaces; to implement the new interface by each class; to override methods move and scale in both classes:  scale should multiply the radius of a circle by the specified factor; scale should multiply widthnnbsp;and height of a rectangle by the specified factor; move should add dx and dy to the center of a circle; move should add dx and dy to the upper-left corner of a rectangle.    
See the provided code and read comments to understand your task better. Now the code is not compiled. 
Note:  do not remove existing classes and their members (including getters and constructors). do not make your classes and interfaces public  
After your changes, the following code should be compiled: MutableShape circle = new Circle(2.0f, 3.5f, 10.1f); circle.move(10.1f, 20.2f); circle.scale(2.2f); ((Circle) circle).getRadius();  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
