
Word constructor   
Suppose we are developing brand names. To come up with something brilliant and just a little bit bizarre, we have decided to combine two words, letter by letter. So first read two strings with letters from the input. 
We also want our new word to be short, therefore, when you run out of characters in one of the strings, just ignore the rest of the letters and print the name you've generated so far.  Sample Input:moewSample Output:meowSample Input:agelakeSample Output:algaekMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
