
Left merge   
Create the body of the function merge_data() that takes two DataFrame objects user_info and emails, merges them using left join and returns the combined DataFrame. You do NOT need to call the function or print any result.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
