
Fahrenheit   
Convert the temperature from Fahrenheit to Celsius in the function below. You can use this formula: 
\(C^\circ = (F^\circ - 32)\times \frac{5}{9}\) 
Round the returned result to 3 decimal places. 
You don't have to handle input, just implement the function below. 
Also, make sure your function returns the value. Please do NOT print anything. 
 Hint   
 You can round a number to 3 decimal places with round(number, 3).  
  Sample Input:451Sample Output:232.778Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
