
Prime numbers   
In math, we call a natural number prime if it's greater than 1 and can be divided without any remainder only by 1 and itself: 
2, 3, 5, 7, 11, 13, 17, ... 
Create a list of all prime numbers up to 1000 in the code below. Just save this list into a variable prime_numbers, you don't have to print anything. 
Make use of any() or all() to check if a number n leaves a zero remainder when divided by values from 2 to n - 1 (inclusively).  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
