
How many days?   
The list seconds is a list of numbers that represent seconds. Convert the number of seconds to full days and print the list that contains these values. The number of full days should be an int value. 
 Hint   
 In case you forgot, there are 60*60*24 seconds in a full day. As for getting the number of full days, use floor division ( //).  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
