
Conditional selection   
Sometimes, we may want to access a piece of information stored in a particular row or a column instead of working with a whole DataFrame. The good news is that Pandas allows us to do it. This is called indexing; we can select a particular subset of aDataFrame or a Series to work with it. 
Selecting 
Before we start, let's import pandas (abbreviated as pd) and create a DataFrame from a dictionary: 
import pandas as pd people = { "first_name": ["Michael", "Michael", 'Jane', 'John'], "last_name": ["Jackson", "Jordan", 'Doe', 'Doe'], "email": ["mjackson@email.com", "mjordan@email.com", 'JaneDoe@email.com', 'JohnDoe@email.com'], "birthday": ["29.09.1958", "17.02.1963", "15.03.1978", "12.05.1979"], "height": [1.75, 1.98, 1.64, 1.8] } df = pd.DataFrame(people) df.head() Output: 
 
We can select any subset of the DataFrame, for example, a single column: 
df['email'] Output: 
 
Now we have a Pandas series with e-mails. 
It's also possible to use df.email. It's called a dot syntax. We can use it for column names without spaces. 
We can also select a list of columns. A Python list requires additional square brackets: 
df[['first_name', 'last_name']] Output: 
 
Now we got a new DataFrame, consisting of these two columns. 
This command always returns a DataFrame, so, even if you select a list that consists of one column, you would return a DataFrame: 
df[['last_name']] Output: 
 
Conditionals 
If we need to introduce a condition to refine our choice, we can include it in square brackets: 
df[df.height nlt; 1.8] Output: 
 
As a result, we returned all columns and rows where the height value is less than 1.8. Note, that it's possible to use square brackets inside this statement, for example, df[df['height'] nlt; 1.8], but we don't need to do it here, as the column name doesn't contain any whitespaces. 
If we need to combine several conditions, we use the following Boolean operators:  namp; for and |(vertical line) for or ~ for not ngt;, nlt;, ngt;=, nlt;=, ==, != for statement comparing.  
Please, don't forget about the parenthesis: 
df[(df.first_name == 'Michael') namp; (df.birthday == '17.02.1963')] Output: 
 
As a result, we returned the rows that match our pre-set condition: "the first name is Michael, birthday is on 17.02.1963". 
One more example with a bit more complex condition. Let's define the first name as Michael or John, height equal or more than 1.8, and the last name should not be Jordan: 
df[((df.first_name == 'Michael') | (df.first_name == 'John')) namp; (df.height ngt;= 1.8) namp; (df.last_name != 'Jordan')] Output: 
 
Note, that we don't use the line break character \, since all new lines are put inside the square brackets. 
If we want to make our filtering exclusive, in other words, to select everything except the indicated parameters, we can add a tilde character ~ and extra parenthesis: 
df[~(((df.first_name == 'Michael') | (df.first_name == 'John')) namp; (df.height ngt;= 1.8) namp; (df.last_name != 'Jordan'))] Output: 
 
Voila! 
Summary 
Now you know how to select:  individual columns or column lists with df[...] individual columns by using dot syntax DataFrame subsets that fall under a set condition  
Of course, the list of various methods goes on. Feel free to experiment.  
