
Vehicle registration plate   
Let's now try to write a regular expression that checks whether a given string follows the format of the vehicle registration plates accepted in India. The basic requirements are stated as follows:  two uppercase Latin letters they are followed by two digits two uppercase Latin letters again and, finally, four digits  
Clusters of letters and digits can be separated by a whitespace character optionally. 
Put your regexp in the template variable. Do not forget that you should check whether the entire string meets the requirements, not only the beginning of the string. 
 Hint   
 To do that, remember the metacharacters that check for the end of the string.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
