
Multilingual dictionary   
Suppose that english, spanish and french are pre-defined lists of n words in English, Spanish and French respectively. 
Imagine that you are developing a multilingual dictionary. Print out the words in three languages in one line, e.g.: 
hello hola bonjour thank you gracias merci 
You can consider the aforementioned lists english, spanish and french defined and use them in your solution.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
