
A single-element tuple   
Alice tried to define a singleton tuple with the first and only item [0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21]. Alas, one small detail is missing here. Fix the code Alice wrote. 
You are NOT supposed to create a new variable for the tuple or print anything.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
