
List from input   
Write a program that takes n numbers as input, creates a list from them, and then prints it. 
The first input line is n â€“ length of the resulting list. It is followed by n lines containing list elements. 
 Hint   
 At this point you may not know how to add elements to a list. You can use the command list.append(element) to do that, where list is the name of your list, and element is the name of the variable that you want to add to the list.  
  Sample Input:5100-17200Sample Output:[100, -1, 72, 0, 0]Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
