
Find even   
Write a program that prints all positive even numbers less than the input number. Please, use the while loop for that. 
The input format: 
The maximum number N varying from 1 to 200. 
The output format: 
All positive even numbers that are less than N. Print them in the ascending order. Each number must be on a separate line.  Sample Input:8Sample Output:246Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
