
Point   
Create a class Point that will represent a point in space. Its constructor needs two parameters \(x\) and \(y\), the coordinates of a point on the plane. The class should have a method dist that takes another instance of Point and returns the Euclidean distance between these two points. For Point(x1, y1) and Point(x2, y2), calculate the distance according to the formula: 
\[d = \sqrt{(x_1 - x_2)^2 + (y_1 - y_2)^2}\]Have a look at the following example: 
p1 = Point(1.5, 1) p2 = Point(1.5, 2) print(p1.dist(p2)) # 1.0 Just create the class, you won't need to do anything else.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
