
Smile for me   
Write a regular expression in the variable template in such a way that it would match the following smileys:  :) :-) :( :-( :o :-o  
Note that your regexp should not match any other smileys or random strings that do not contain them.   Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
