
Printable   
Write a code that for the given integer code point checks whether this code point corresponds to a printable character (as opposed to a hexadecimal escape sequence), and if yes, outputs this character, otherwise outputs False. 
 Hint   
 Printable range is from 32 to 126, including these numbers.  
  Sample Input:126Sample Output:~Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
