Template Method Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Now, we'll add annbsp;new concrete class Sandwich 
Sandwich is different from Steak, so that's why you need to implement it. 
The first line of the standard input is the concrete meal. 
You must output the meal procedure. 
Please do not change the provided code of the classes.  Sample Input:SandwichSample Output:Ingredients: bacon, white bread, egg, cheese, mayonnaise, tomatoPaste ingredients between bread slices. Toast sandwichThat's goodLick fingers and go to sleepMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
