
Beautify both output and code   
The output should be user-friendly, but the code part is also important. Well-structured and readable code is very important for being a good programmer. Now it's up to you to decide, which formatting method to choose. 
Imagine you need to compose a dynamic URL for every certain user with user-specific details. Suppose, you want to send different URLs for every user, depending on their name and profession. The base would be something like 
"http://example.com/*nickname*/desirable/*profession*/profile", where nickname and profession are prompts from a user and are dynamic. 
Read the nickname and profession of the user from the input and print a user-specific URL. Don't bother about any rules of composing the URLs and just use raw input to accomplish the task.  Sample Input:raybeamcereal-killerSample Output:http://example.com/raybeam/desirable/cereal-killer/profileSample Input:AnnMelonbodybuilderSample Output:http://example.com/AnnMelon/desirable/bodybuilder/profileMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
