
Coordinates   
Locate a point on the Cartesian coordinate plane: which of four quadrants does a point belong to? 
 
Read two numbers from the input, not necessarily integers, the first number will indicate a position on the X-axis, the second one â€” on the Y-axis. Let's keep referring to the quadrants by Roman numerals, as shown in the picture. 
If a point is the origin (0, 0), print "It's the origin!". In case of a point lying on the axes, with either x = 0 or y = 0, print "One of the coordinates is equal to zero!".  Sample Input:3.987-10Sample Output:IVMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
