
Let's rock   
There are many bands in the world that perform all kinds of music. Let's suppose for a second that you're a fan of rock and want to create a program that deals with rock bands. 
For that, you obviously need the class RockBand with such attributes as genre ("rock") and key_instruments (by default, a list ["electric guitar", "drums"]). Let's also, for the sake of simplicity, assume n_members to be a class attribute equal to 4, since most rock bands do have 4 members. 
Create this class and an object of that class: name the variable after any rock band that you like. Print the attributes of your rock band on separate lines in this order: genre, n_members, key_instruments. 
 Hint   
 Make sure that the attributes have correct types: genre is a string, n_members is an integer, and key_instruments is a list.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
