
Series   
As you already know, pandas is a popular Python library for data manipulation. This topic will introduce you to Series, a basic one-dimensional data structure in pandas. 
Series is a building block to the 2D data structure in pandas, DataFrame. The latter is the one you will use the most in practice. So, while it is important to have some idea of Series, in-depth knowledge of its functionality is not necessary. 
Before we start, do not forget that you need to import pandas to be able to use all of its functionality, including Series. Note that traditionally, the name of the library is abbreviated as pd in the import statement: 
import pandas as pd 
What is Series Series is a one-dimensional array. For example, here is a Series that stores names of the students on a machine learning class: 
 
You can notice that each element stored in a Series is associated with a label called index. By default, this index is just the sequence 0, 1, 2, ... . However, any custom values can be used. For example, we can store ages of the students in a Series, and set students' names as row identifiers so that we know which student the age corresponds to: 
 
Cool, but how do you create such a Series object? There are several ways to do so. 
Converting other data structures to Series 
If the data is already stored in some other data structure, you can easily convert it to Series as shown below: 
ages_list = [21, 20, 25, 22] names_list = ['Anna', 'Bob', 'Maria', 'Jack'] ages_series = pd.Series(ages_list, index=names_list, name='Age') print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Maria 25 # Jack 22 # Name: Age, dtype: int64 Here, we convert a list of students' ages ages_list into a Series object ages_series. We also assign a custom index, students' names stored in the list names_list, using the index keyword. If we fail to provide the values for the index, values 0, 1, 2, 3 would be assigned. Finally, we can also give our Series a name by specifying the optional name parameter. 
Similarly, you can convert a Python dictionary into a Series object. Note that dictionary keys (students' names in the example below) will automatically become the indexes in the new Series. Cool, right? 
student_ages_dict = {'Anna': 21, 'Bob': 20, 'Maria': 25, 'Jack': 22} ages_series = pd.Series(student_ages_dict, name='Ages') print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Maria 25 # Jack 22 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64  You can always change index later by modifying the index attribute of the Series: 
ages_series.index = ['A', 'B', 'M', 'J'] print(ages_series) # A 21 # B 20 # M 25 # J 22 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64  
 Of course, the length of the data and index you provide should coincide. Otherwise, an error will occur.  
 
Modifying a Series object 
Series is value-mutable; you can easily change the values stored in a Series, for example by accessing them by index. To illustrate this, let's update Jack's age: 
ages_series['Jack'] = 23 print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Maria 25 # Jack 23 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64 However, a Series object is size-immutable: once it's created, no elements can be added to or removed from it. It is made on purpose, to efficiently store Series in memory. 
But what should you do if you need to add or drop some values to/from a Series? No worries, appending, and removing elements is still possible. However, the result of these operations will be a new Series object. 
For example, let's remove Maria's record from our Series. This can be done with the drop method.: 
new_ages_series = ages_series.drop(index='Maria') print(new_ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Jack 23 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64 Note that the original Series remained unchanged: 
print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Maria 25 # Jack 23 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64 If you want the returned Series to be automatically assigned to the original one, you can specify the optional inplace parameter to be True : 
ages_series.drop(index='Maria', inplace=True) print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Jack 23 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64 To add new records to Series, one can explicitly specify the value for the new index. Let's add Maria's record back to the ages_series: 
ages_series['Maria'] = 25 print(ages_series) # Anna 21 # Bob 20 # Jack 23 # Maria 25 # Name: Ages, dtype: int64 Note that this syntax is introduced for convenience. Since Series is size-immutable, behind the scenes, a new Series with the newly added element will be created and automatically assigned to the original one. 
Operations on Series 
The key feature of pandas is that operations between several Series automatically align the data based on the index. 
Let's imagine we have two Series, algebra and calculus, containing students' exam results for Algebra and Calculus courses respectively: 
 
Suppose we want to compute the average score students got for the two exams. 
average = 0.5*(algebra + calculus) print(average) # Anna 75.0 # Bob 90.0 # Jack 80.0 # Maria 90.0 # dtype: float64 Note that the order of the students in the two Series, algebraand calculus, is different, and yet the averages are computed correctly. Very convenient! 
Alright, but what happens if some indexes from one Series don't exist in the other one? Let's imagine there was also the third exam on Probability, but only Anna and Bob took it. The results are stored in the probability Series: 
 
What will happen if we try to compute the average of the three Series now? 
average = 0.33*(algebra + calculus + probability) print(average) # Anna 82.5 # Bob 92.4 # Jack NaN # Maria NaN # dtype: float64 As you can see, the result of an operation between unaligned Series has the union of the indexes involved. If a label is not found in one of the operands, the result will be marked as a missing value NaN. 
Writing code without doing any explicit data alignment gives a lot of flexibility in data analysis. The integrated data alignment in pandas is what sets the library apart from the majority of related tools for working with labeled data. 
Conclusions  Series is a one-dimensional data structure in pandas. Series store values along with their labels called indexes. Series is value-mutable but size-immutable: one can modify values stored in it, but cannot add new values to or remove values from it. When performing operations on several Series objects, they are automatically aligned on the index.    Show topic summary
