  
If attributes define the data that the objects of a particular class have, the methods define their behavior. Python has several types of methods that you can create within a class but, in this topic, we will focus on the instance methods.  
Method syntax 
Methods define the functionality of the objects that belong to the particular class. The basic syntax looks like this: 
# basic method syntax class MyClass: # the constructor def __init__(self, arg1): self.att = arg1 # custom method def do_smt(self): # does something You can see that declaring a method resembles declaring a function: we have keyword def followed by the name of the method. The parameters of the method are written inside the parentheses.  
The first parameter of the method should always be self. You may remember that self represents the particular instance of the class. When it comes to instance methods, the first parameter that is passed to the method is the instance that called it. Let's create an instance of MyClass and see how this works: 
my_object = MyClass(some_value) # calling the instance method my_object.do_smt() # my_object does something In this example, the my_object instance is passed implicitly so we do not write the parameter in the code. We can, however, pass the instance explicitly: 
MyClass.do_smt(my_object) # my_object does the same thing These examples clearly illustrate why self has to be the first argument of the instance methods. If you want your method to have other parameters, just write them after the self keyword! 
Methods vs functions 
Though they are quite similar, Python does make a distinction between methods and functions. To quote the official documentation, "a method is a function that 'belongs to' an object." Since we're interested in OOP, we'll specifically be looking at methods associated with class instances. 
Let's consider an example: 
# class and its methods class Ship: def __init__(self, name, capacity): self.name = name self.capacity = capacity self.cargo = 0 def sail(self): print("{} has sailed!".format(self.name)) # function def sail_function(name): print("{} has sailed!".format(name)) What is of interest to us here is the method sail of the class Ship and the function sail_function. Let's call them: 
# creating an instance of the class Ship # and calling the method sail black_pearl = Ship("Black Pearl", 800) black_pearl.sail() # prints "Black Pearl has sailed!" # calling the function sail_function sail_function(black_pearl.name) # also prints "Black Pearl has sailed!" The way that we've defined them, both our method and our function produce the same results but in a different way. A method is connected to an object of the class, it is not independent the way a function is. Sure they are both called by their names, but to call a method we need to invoke the class that this method belongs to.  
Return 
So far the method hasn't returned any values since we only used the print() function. Obviously, just as with functions, we can define what type of data the method can return with the return statement. For example, let's create a method that calculates how many kilograms of cargo the ship has (initially, the weight of the cargo is given in tons): 
class Ship: # other methods def convert_cargo(self): return self.cargo * 1000 The method is simple: it converts the tons into kilograms (by multiplying it by 1000) and then returns the calculated value. If we were to call it, we wouldn't get any messages unless we explicitly printed the result of the function: 
print(black_pearl.convert_cargo()) # 0 Since we haven't changed the default value of the cargo attribute, the method would return 0 multiplied by 1000, which is also 0. 
Summary 
Methods within classes specify the behavior of class or its objects. They are similar to functions with the exception that they are strongly connected to the class and cannot be called independently from it or its instances.  
The first parameter of instance methods is the keyword self that represents the particular instance of the class. That particular instance of the class is the first argument that is passed to the method. Methods can return values or simply print messages (i.e. return nothing). 
Methods allow you to add any functionality to your classes. This is how you can manipulate your objects and create complex programs, so we encourage you to explore methods in your projects!  
