
Heavy task   
Here you have a part of the Penguins dataset: 
 
The body_mass_g column has the float data type. Select the rows with penguins heavier than 4.5 kilograms and print the result. 
Note, the DataFrame is already loaded as penguins_df  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
