
Math from NumPy   
Mathematics is often useful in programming. Let's solve one math problem using the math library.  
Your task is to implement the calculate_cosine() function. The function parameter is an angle in degrees. The function should calculate the cosine of the given angle using the corresponding math.cos() function from the math library, then round the result to two decimal places using the round(..., 2) function, and print it. 
But it's not so simple. Read the documentation for this function and pay attention to what unit of measure the angle must be in. 
You can find the additional function you need on the same page in the Angular conversion section. 
Do not forget to import the necessary library. Don't call the function, just implement it.  Sample Input:0Sample Output:1.0Sample Input:60Sample Output:0.5Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
