
Catchy song   
Have you ever dreamed of becoming a songwriter? It's time to make a hit. We will leave a verse for later and write the chorus part instead. 
All you need to do is to read the input number n and an input word (they are given on separate lines) and to repeat this word exactly n times. Don't specify any message when reading the input. 
Finally, print your song for us, please! 
 Hint   
 You can multiply a string by an integer, e.g. 'a' * 5 will give you this string 'aaaaa'.  
  Sample Input:7laSample Output:lalalalalalalaMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
