
Lucky 7   
Read an integer number n. This is a number of integer values you will receive on the next n lines. Among these numbers find the multiples of 7 (that is, numbers that could be divided by 7 without the remainder) and print their squares. Each square number should be printed on a new line.  
 Hint   
 You can write n to some variable and then call input() function exactly n times using for loop. 
 
You can either output each square immediately after reading the input with the number, or you can calculate all the squares at first and then output them. It doesn't matter which option you choose: the only thing that matters is that you should output m lines with correct squares.  
  Sample Input:7811-49035641433Sample Output:24010196Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
