
Matching username requirements   
You need to write a simple program that checks whether usernames match the requirements. The only requirement is that it has to begin with a letter.   If a username starts with anything but a letter, your program should return Oops! The username has to start with a letter. Otherwise, output Thank you!  
You will get a username as input. Return a correct response.  Sample Input:12userSample Output:Oops! The username has to start with a letter.Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
