
Favorable default   
Write a short function code that will print out this message: 
We code in {language} 
Set "Python" as a default value to the language parameter.  
You don't need to call the function, you only need to implement it.   Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
