
Largest city   
One way to compare different cities is to compare their population. You've created a class City and objects of this class have parameters name and population. 
Define the __init__ method and __gt__ method that would compare two cities based on their population.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
