
Decimal places   
Round the number from input to the required number of decimals. 
The input format: 
Two lines: the first with a floating-point number, the second with an integer representing the decimal count. 
The output format: 
A formatted string containing the rounded number. 
 
 Do NOT forget to convert the input numbers and to enclose each value in {} in a formatted string.  
 
 Hint   
 We encourage you to use string formatting, since solutions with round() function may not pass the tests. Besides, this is exactly what the topic is about!  You can use .{decimal_count}f formatting specification to round the number to the required number of decimals.  
  Sample Input:2.718283Sample Output:2.718Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
