
Error   
The code below is supposed to write years from 2010 to 2020 to the file years.txt. However, something's wrong with the code.  
Find the mistake and fix it. 
 Hint   
 You cannot access the file after it's been closed.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 5 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
