
Desks   
 
 Wow! This problem is kind of tricky. If you're ready to put your thinking cap on, brace yourself and good luck! Otherwise, you can skip it for now and return any time later.  
 
A school has decided to create three new math groups and equip three classrooms for them with new desks. At most two students may sit at any desk. The number of students in each of the three groups is known. Output the smallest number of desks to be purchased. 
Each group will sit in its own classroom. 
Input data format: 
The program receives the input of three non-negative integers: the number of students in each of the three classes (the numbers do not exceed 1000). 
 Hint   
 You should find the number of desks in each classroom independently and then sum the three numbers to get the total one.  
  Sample Input:202122Sample Output:32Sample Input:161820Sample Output:27Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 1 second Show topic summary
