
Growing square   
In Sample Input you see a dataset df. Change the dataset so that you get the dataset from Sample Output. You don't need to print the resulting DataFrame, just make sure that all the changes are saved in the DataFrame.  Sample Input: a b0 1 21 4 5Sample Output: a b c0 1 2 31 4 5 62 7 8 9Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
