
Implementing logic   
Advanced input() handling is used to read input directly into several variables, e. g.,  
name, surname = input().split(), but a user still can enter more or fewer words.  
In this task, you have to make sure that the user entered the necessary amount of words and...  If there are more or fewer words in the input, print an error: "You need to enter exactly 2 words. Try again!" If everything's good, greet the user personally.   Sample Input:Anthony StarkSample Output:Welcome to our party, Anthony StarkSample Input:Steven Rogers Captain AmericaSample Output:You need to enter exactly 2 words. Try again!Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
