
Concatenation with the separator   
Write a concat() function that will take an arbitrary number of strings and combine them into one through a separator (the keyword argument sep). If no separator is specified, then it should separate the strings by spaces: 
print(concat("turtle")) # "turtle" print(concat("cat", "dog")) # "cat dog" print(concat("a", "b", "c", sep=":")) # "a:b:c" You do not need to call a function, just implement it. 
 Hint   
 Consider using sep.join(strings) for concatenating arguments from your tuple.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
