
Hero damage   Let's now take a look at how global variables can help us to save information between different function calls. 
 
Imagine you're writing a program for some video game: you need to calculate the damage that the main hero deals to its enemies in one hit. The current damage is stored in the global variable hero_damage. Use the power of this global and write three functions that change its value:  double_damage() doubles the damage of the hero disarmed() makes the damage equal to 10% of the current value power_potion() adds 100 damage points  
The functions are already declared. You only need to replace passkeyword with some code of yours.  
Don't output or return anything, just write the body of the functions. Remember how we can change the value of a global variable.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
