Movie Open on Hyperskill

  
You are given a class named Movie. Write two constructors for the class. 
The first constructor should take three arguments (title, desc, year) and initialize the corresponding fields. 
The second one should take only two arguments (title, year) and initialize title and year. In this case, the field desc should have a value "empty". 
Use the provided template, do not change it.  Memory limit: 256 MbTime limit: 5s
Show topic summary
