
Cities   
Imagine you've created a program that plays the cities game with a user. For the game to work, you need to remember the user's city and be able to change it. Below is the code that does that, but there's a missing line in it. Fix this problem! 
You only need to add one line. Please, don't change the rest of the code.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
