Shapes area Open on JetBrains Academy

  
You have five classes: Shape, Triangle, Circle, Square, and Rectangle. The class Shape has a method area(). This method does nothing. Override the method in all subclasses. Overridden methods should return an area of a particular figure. Use class fields for this. 
The area of a triangle is \( S = bh / 2 \) where \( h \) is the height of the triangle, \( b \) is the base of the triangle. 
The area of a circle is \( S = \pi R^2 \) where \( R \) is the radius of the circle. For \( \pi \) use Math.PI constant. 
The area of a square is \( S = s^2 \) where \( s \) is the length of the side of the square. 
The area of a rectangle is \( S = wh \) where \( w \)nnbsp;is the width of the rectangle and \( h \) the height of the rectangle.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
