
Set new index   
You are working with df_rock DataFrame that contains sonar signals from two object classes: rocks and mines. In the first four columns, you can see waves lengths that got the sonar from different angles. The last two columns, called name and label respectively, contain an individual object key and the category of an object: rock or mine. 
Suppose that now, for convenience, you want to set the column called name as index. 
You can see a dataset sample below. Note, df_rock is a variable name that contains the whole DataFrame. Just insert your code before the print() function.  Sample Input: zero_deg sixty_deg ninety_deg straight_angle name label0 0.437427 0.127416 0.258251 0.425674 EAO2 Mine1 0.421407 0.439730 0.560459 0.424267 PD38 Mine2 0.205278 0.434688 0.398431 0.532222 JL46 Rock3 0.094910 0.132226 0.105227 0.156142 M7V9 Rock4 0.314031 0.272306 0.057900 0.486960 PIYW RockSample Output:Index(['EAO2', 'PD38', 'JL46', 'M7V9', 'PIYW'], dtype='object', name='name')Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
