
Underworld   
Charon the Ferryman carries souls across the river Styx to the world of the dead but does so only for a fee. It's a business after all. 
Check whether the recently deceased has a coin, if any, print Welcome to Charon's boat! 
The variable coin stores a Boolean value, so it qualifies as a condition. If coin has False value, alas! There's nothing to be done about it. 
In conclusion, let's warn everyone in the underworld (both those in the boat and those overboard) by printing the message There is no turning back.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
