
English contractions   
Lucy is drawing a poster with English contractions for her students. We will join her English club and help with learning materials. 
Print the following strings with contractions: 
I am = I'm I have = I've I will = I'll I had / would = I'd Each string should be on a new line. This will be easy if you use quotes wisely.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
