
Girl Power   
Imagine you have a full Penguins dataset: 
penguins_df.head()  
Select the columns 'species', 'island', 'sex' and all the rows with 'FEMALE' value in the sex column, then print the resulting DataFrame.   Hint   
 It's easier to use .loc here. Take a look at this code snippet from the theory to solve the task: 
 
df.loc[df.birthday == '12.05.1979', 'last_name':'birthday':2] Output: 
 
  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
