
Movie night   
Write the class Movie and define the class constructor with such parameters as the title, director, and the year of release.  
In the corresponding variables defined below, create such objects as the "Titanic" (James Cameron, 1997), "Star Wars" (George Lucas, 1977), and "Fight Club" (David Fincher, 1999).  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
