
Double greeting   
We wrote a function that greets two people: 
def greeting(first_name, second_name): print("Hello,", first_name, "and", second_name) The first name is already stored in the variable name_1, and the second is stored in the variable name_2. Your task is to call this function twice in the code section. The first time it should print Hello, name_1 and name_2, and the second time Hello, name_2 and name_1.  Sample Input:SidNancySample Output:Hello, Sid and NancyHello, Nancy and SidMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
