
Thats how we prepare these tasks   
Imagine you have a full Penguins dataset: 
penguins_df.head()  
Take only species, body_mass_g, and sex columns and put the selection into the selecting_task variable. Note that the DataFrame is already loaded as penguins_df.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
