Publication and its subclasses Open on JetBrains Academy

  
You are given four classes â€”nnbsp;Publication, Newspaper, Article and Announcement. You need to override methods getType() and getDetails() in classes inherited from the class Publication. 
Then you need to implement getInfo() in the class Publicationnnbsp;usingnnbsp;getType() and getDetails(). The method should return a String with a type of publication in the first place, then details in round brackets and the title after a colon. Examples are shown below.  Sample Input:Publication; The new eraSample Output:Publication: The new eraSample Input:Newspaper; Football results; Sport newsSample Output:Newspaper (source - Sport news): Football resultsSample Input:Article; Why the Sun is hot; Dr James SmithSample Output:Article (author - Dr James Smith): Why the Sun is hotSample Input:Announcement; Will sell a house; 30Sample Output:Announcement (days to expire - 30): Will sell a houseMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
