Shape hierarchy Open on JetBrains Academy

  
You have an abstract class Shape with two abstract methods: getPerimeter()and getArea(). See the provided code template. 
nnbsp; 
 
nnbsp; 
You need to declare and implement three classes: Triangle, Rectangle and Circle. The classes must extend the Shape class and implement all abstract methods. To implement the methods the standard class Math may help you. 
Note: do NOT make your classes public. 
- The class Triangle must have a constructor with three double arguments for setting the length of each side. To calculate the area of this shape you may use the Heron's formula. 
- The class Rectangle must have a constructor with two double arguments for setting the length of different sides. 
- The class Circle must have a constructor with one double argument for setting the radius. You may use Math.PI as the PI constant or you can declare it yourself. 
nnbsp; 
Examples 
A circle has a radius = 10: perimeter = 62.831853..., area = 314.159265.... 
A triangle has three sides a = 3, b = 4 and c = 5: perimeter = 12.0, area = 6.0. 
A rectangle has two different sides a = 5, b = 10: perimeter = 30.0, area = 50.0.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
