
The Louvre   
You are writing a program that deals with the paintings that hang in the Louvre. You've created a class Painting and are planning to add some class methods and a class constructor. 
What'll be common for all paintings is that they all belong to the same museum, obviously, but the differences will be in the title of the painting, the painter and the year of creation. 
Finish writing the class Painting and then process some information from the input. 
The input format: 
The input contains 3 lines: the first is the title of the painting, the second with the artist and the third with the year of the creation. 
The output format: 
A string of the kind: "Title" by Artist (Year) hangs in the Louvre. 
 Hint   
 Think about which information should be in the class variables, and which in the instance variables.  
  Sample Input:Mona LisaLeonardo da Vinci1503Sample Output:"Mona Lisa" by Leonardo da Vinci (1503) hangs in the Louvre.Sample Input:The Fortune TellerCaravaggio1600Sample Output:"The Fortune Teller" by Caravaggio (1600) hangs in the Louvre.Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
