
Decypher a message   
Let's decypher a little message. The first input line is an encoded message, and the second line is the key integer number. Convert the key to two bytes and sum up its items. Then add the resulting sum to the code point of each character in the message. Finally, print the decoded message.  Sample Input:HlAdghmcXnt256Sample Output:ImBehindYouMemory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
