
Number of users   
There is a JSON file users.json. The file has already been created and filled with data. 
It has the following structure: 
{ "users": [ { "name": "John", "last_name": "Doe", "age": 33 }, ... ] } Find out how many users are defined in this file and print this number. 
Note that the json module has already been imported, you don't need to import it again! 
 Hint   
 Convert the JSON file to a dictionary and get the size of the list of users.  
  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
