
Sum of numbers   
Write a program that takes two integer numbers x and y and then prints the sum of these numbers. 
Variables x and y are already defined for you. Use the sum() function, please. 
 Hint   
 You have noticed that sum() function requires numbers to be in parentheses, haven't you?  
  Sample Input:811Sample Output:19Sample Input:93542Sample Output:977Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Show topic summary
