Concat positive numbers Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Implement a method to concatenate all positive numbers of two input ArrayLists to a single resultingnnbsp;list. 
At first, elements from the first ArrayListnnbsp;shoud go, and then the elements from the second ArrayList.  Sample Input:8 11 -2 -3 14 15-1 33 12 -3 -5Sample Output:8 11 14 15 33 12Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
