
Solar system   
Create a file planets.txt and write the names of the Solar system planets there, each on a new line. In total, the file should contain 8 lines with the following planets: Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, and Neptune. 
When opening the file, specify encoding='utf-8'.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
