
Mountain high   
Objects of the class Mountain have an attribute height defined in its constructor. The value is initially given in meters. 
Create a method convert_height that converts the height of the mountain from meters to feet according to the formula \(Foot = Meter / 0.3048\) and then returns the calculated value. This method doesn't take any attributes except for self.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
