Handling interruptions Open on JetBrains Academy    
The class CounterThread extends Thread and overrides the run method. The method increments the counter variable in a loop. As it is now, the loop works infinitely. You should fix it by adding interruption handling. If another thread interrupts this thread, it must print "It was interrupted" and stop. Please, do not remove the loop. Otherwise, your solution may not pass tests.  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds Show topic summary
