
Football tournament   
You are organizing a local football tournament. At the initial state, each team plays against every other one once. 
The list teams contains the names of the participating teams. Which games will be played? Print out all of them. 
For example, if teams = ['Best-ever', 'Not-so-good', 'Amateurs'], your output should look like as follows: 
('Best-ever', 'Not-so-good') ('Best-ever', 'Amateurs') ('Not-so-good', 'Amateurs')  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check. 
