
Stack manipulation   
Given the number n and a sequence of n stack operations, print out the content of the stack after performing them (starting from the top element). 
You can assume that originally the stack is empty. 
Input: 
The first line is the number n. The next n lines represent stack operations in the format: OPERATION [element]. Work with the input and process the given operations. 
Output: 
Elements in the stack, from top to bottom, each on a new line. 
 Hint   
 Use split(" ") to split the input string on the whitespace.  
  Sample Input:4PUSH 1PUSH 10POPPUSH 8Sample Output:81Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
