Publications Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Below you can see four classes: Publication, Newspaper, Article and Announcement. 
You need to override the method getDetails() in the classes inherited from the class Publication. Thesennbsp;classes should use getDetails() from Publication to get information about the title and append their own additional data. 
Examples are shown below.  Sample Input:Publication; The new eraSample Output:title="The new era"Sample Input:Newspaper; Football results; Sport newsSample Output:title="Football results", source="Sport news"Sample Input:Article; Why the Sun is hot; Dr James SmithSample Output:title="Why the Sun is hot", author="Dr James Smith"Sample Input:Announcement; Will sell a house; 30Sample Output:title="Will sell a house", daysToExpire=30Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
