
Hack the Pentagon   
There's a hidden variable with top secret data. You can't see it, and all you know about it is that it's called pentagon_passwords and that it is a container with sets. Try to get the intersection of these sets and output the number of elements in it.   Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
