
Converting a list to Series   
Suppose that list foods contains the names of different foods, and calories is a list that contains the corresponding calorie content per 100g. 
Define a function that creates and returns a Series object that stores values from the calories list while having the names from foods as index. Also, set the name of the Series to 'Calorie content'. 
NOTE: you do NOT need to print your result. 
For example, suppose that: 
foods = ['bagel', 'pasta', 'rice'] calories = [310, 110, 140] Then, your function should return the following Series: bagel 310 pasta 110 rice 140 Name: Calorie content, dtype: int64  Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds Caution You may see errors in your code or execution results due to missing context. Donâ€™t worry about it, just write the solution and press Check.  Show topic summary
