Count words Open on JetBrains Academy

  
Read an input text from the console and print the number of words. By word we mean a sequence of characters separated by one or several spaces. 
If the input is empty or there arennbsp;no characters except spaces, print 0.  Sample Input:one two threeSample Output:3Sample Input:between us several space charactersSample Output:5Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 8 seconds
Show topic summary
