
Finding capitalized words   
Your task is to write a program that finds all capitalized words and digits in an input string. Please print them in the same order as in the the example output.  Sample Input:Albert Einstein was born in 1879. His IQ has been estimated to be between 160 and 180.Sample Output:Capitalized words: Albert, Einstein, His, IQDigits: 1879, 160, 180Memory limit: 256 MBTime limit: 15 seconds
